{
    "subject": "resource/Karl_Anselm,_4th_Prince_of_Thurn_and_Taxis",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Frankfurt",
    "human_readable": "Karl Anselm, 4th Prince of Thurn and Taxis was born in Frankfurt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9797325134277344,
            "question": "Where was Karl Anselm, 4th Prince of Thurn and Taxis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5270200967788696,
            "question": "To which princely family did Karl Anselm belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048722624778748,
            "question": "Are there any famous people born in Frankfurt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47119539976119995,
            "question": "What was the title held by Karl Anselm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3728927969932556,
            "question": "What other information might be useful to know about Karl Anselm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14956578612327576,
            "question": "Is Frankfurt a large city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12034504115581512,
            "question": "What are some common birthplaces for royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1029893085360527,
            "question": "Can you name a city in Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04462769627571106,
            "question": "What is the significance of place of birth in historical records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03043721243739128,
            "question": "What is the full name of the person mentioned in the statement?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Anselm, 4th Prince of Thurn and Taxis was born in Frankfurt.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8320_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of place of birth in historical records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8320_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a city in Germany?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8320_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common birthplaces for royalty?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8320_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8320_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the answer to your question:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention of Karl Anselm's birthplace in the documents. The only information related to his birth is in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8320/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt, where it mentions \"Karl Anselm was the eldest son of Alexander Ferdinand 3rd and his first wife Margravine Sophie Christine of Brandenburg-Bayreuth.\" which does not provide information about Karl Anselm's birthplace."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Karl Anselm, 4th Prince of Thurn and Taxis, being born in Frankfurt. Instead, the information focuses on his roles and familial relationships but does not specify his place of birth."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Karl Anselm, 4th Prince of Thurn and Taxis was born in Stuttgart, not Frankfurt.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Alexander Ferdinand moved the principal residence of the Princely House from Frankfurt to Regensburg when he relocated the Diet.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Karl Anselm was the eldest son of Alexander Ferdinand 3rd and his first wife Margravine Sophie Christine of Brandenburg-Bayreuth, but it is stated that Alexander Ferdinand moved the principal residence from Frankfurt to Regensburg.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Karl Anselm was born on 2 June 1733, and while he did serve as Prinzipalkommissar at the Perpetual Imperial Diet in Regensburg from 1773 to 1797, there is no information suggesting he was born in Frankfurt.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}